Okay, so I'm talking about Glance here, and I'm building this to help small teams keep track of the work that they're handing off to AI agents and their background jobs.
And I think this is important because it's catching not only that jobs ran, but it's also checking that business expectations are met.
So here I logged in, and I could see that I have some failing jobs here.
So I have 98 are passing.
I've acknowledged one warning and one failing.
So if I dig into this, I could see these two that require my attention.
So one, for my Psyched Music, it's telling me that the Buffer failed posts need to be cleared.
So this is, I mean, I happen to know what this is, but it's saying that there was six failures and that this alert goes off when there's five or more.
And it gives me, so it tells me exactly what's going on.
I could actually see the remediation right here, what I need to do to fix it.
And I could also just hit copy details, and it just gives me all the information about this monitor remediation and what's running it.
So I could actually paste this into an agent to help me fix it.
And if I jump in and look at the configuration here, I could actually see how it works.
And basically, every time a job runs, a payload comes in, and I could configure whatever I want to look at based on that JSON payload that comes in with each of the checks.
And I could set up different monitors to fail at different times, including whether a value is how it compares to what my expectation was.
Or I could look at the average over some number of runs as well.
So I could say, hey, I only want to make sure that this only has a total of five failures over the course of a week or something like that.
And then once I'm happy with what's going on with the monitor, I could just acknowledge it, and it gets acknowledged and closed down.
Here's another.
Again, these are all demo ones I sent up.
But here's another one where I actually have a job running that does a nightly refactor of the code base.
And it failed for some reason.
And the reason it's telling me it failed here is that it actually has a PR from a previous night that was sitting in GitHub waiting to be merged and wasn't merged.
So I could actually use remediation to see what's going on.
I could see that job is sitting right here.
So I could go and merge that job, and then I could just acknowledge this alert as well.
So now when I come into my dashboard, I see that everything's passing.
And then this is, like, super easy to set up.
So now I'm going to go and merge that job.